http://www.univairparts.com/privacy-policy/

Loading... Please wait...
Wish Lists
View Cart (0)
Shop by Brand
Univair Bendix Cleveland Precision LP Aero Plastics Goodyear Poly-Fiber Delco Randolph Whelen
View All Brands
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Univair respects your privacy. We do not give or sell our customer information to outside organizations. Below are the ways in which Univair collects and uses your personal information.
Customer Accounts
Personal and financial information you provide to us during the checkout process is used only for payment processing and order fulfillment. This information is required on all orders regardless of how the order is submitted (via website, mail, phone, or fax).
Information collected when creating an account includes your full name, billing and shipping addresses, email, and phone number.
Guest Checkout
Customers who do not wish to create an account can make a purchase as a guest. We collect the same payment information listed above when making a purchase, however an account is not created in our web database. Guests do not have access to account features (such as order history and wish lists), however you will still receive status updates and tracking numbers via email.
Payment Information
Due to our compliance with PCI Security Standards, credit card and PayPal information is NOT stored in your account or in our web database. Payment information is sent directly to our payment processor, PayPal, when you submit an order through our website. For information on how PayPal stores and protects your data, please visit the PayPal website and review their security policy.
Order Notifications
Customers will receive email communications from Univair when they successfully place an order, and when the status of their order changes. These email notifications include order confirmations/receipts, status updates, shipping confirmations and tracking numbers. When checking out, even as a guest, please make sure to use a valid email address, otherwise you will not receive your tracking numbers. If you are not receiving email notifications from us, please check your spam filter.
Univair.com utilizes an Abandoned Shopping Cart function, which will store items in your shopping cart for up to 30 days, or until you complete the checkout process. You may receive an email notice reminding you that the items in your cart are still available for purchase. After 30 days of inactivity, your cart is automatically emptied and you will not receive any more notifications.
Email/Newsletter Subscribe
Univair publishes a monthly email newsletter that is sent to customers who subscribe to our email marketing list. More information on how consent is obtained and how you can revoke your consent (unsubscribe) is explained below.
WHAT WE EMAIL YOUAnyone who is subscribed to our email marketing list will receive our monthly newsletter, featuring articles of interest pertaining to general aviation, notice of sales and special promotions, dates of upcoming aviation events, fly-ins and seminars, and other information we think our subscribers might find pertinent.
We generally email only once per month, however we reserve the right to email subscribers more or less frequently as business conditions warrant.
HOW WE COLLECT EMAIL ADDRESSESUnivair collects customer email addresses through both IMPLIED CONSENT and EXPRESS CONSENT (explained below). You will be added to our email subscription list when you do one of the following:
Make a purchase from Univair through our website (IMPLIED CONSENT). However, you can opt out of the list by unchecking the "Hear From Us Via Email?" boxes during the checkout process (found on "Step 4: Order Confirmation" page).
Enter your name and email address in the "Email Subscribe" form in the footer of our website (EXPRESS CONSENT).
Text the word "UNIVAIR" to 22828. You will receive a follow up text asking you to text us your email address (EXPRESS CONSENT).
HOW TO UNSUBSCRIBEYou can unsubscribe from our marketing/newsletter list at any time by doing one of the following:
Click the "UNSUBSCRIBE" link in the bottom of any marketing email.
Reply to any marketing email from Univair with a request to remove you from our list. The email address you reply from will be the email we remove, unless you specify otherwise.
Email newsletter@univair.com with a request to remove you from our list. Be sure to include the exact email address(es) you want removed.
Note that unsubscribing from Order Notifications is not possible (see details above).
DATA SHARINGEmail contacts collected by Univair are used only by us. We do not sell or give our email subscription list to anyone.
Cookies
Cookies are used for website functionality only and do not collect any personally identifiable information, nor do they track your web browsing habits outside of our website. Please make sure your browser preferences are set to allow cookies from this website, otherwise the shopping cart and checkout functions will not work properly.
Google Analytics
Univair utilizes Google Analytics for the purpose of understanding how users find and use our website, for tracking ROI for online marketing, and for search engine optimization (SEO) purposes. For further information on how Google Analytics collects and uses data, please visit their website and review their privacy policy.
Univair Aircraft Corporation
2500 Himalaya Road
Aurora, Colorado 80011
Toll Free Sales: 888-433-5433
Phone: 303-375-8882
Fax: 303-375-8888
Quick Links
Pages
Privacy Policy
»
Interactive Parts Catalogs
»
Service Bulletins and Memos
»
Airworthiness Directives
»
SAIBs
»
Safety Alerts for Operators
»
Type Certificate Data Sheets
»
Supplemental Type Certificates
»
Technical Resources
»
FAA-PMA Eligibility List
»
AN Hardware Guide
»
Decimal Equivalents Chart
»
Type Clubs and Organizations
»
Photo Gallery
»
Aviation Links
»
newsletter
Subscribe to our email newsletter to receive information on special sales and promotions, upcoming events, and articles of interest regarding general aviation.
Name
Email
Or text UNIVAIR to 22828 to subscribe to our email list. Message and data rates may apply. You can unsubscribe by using the 'unsubscribe' link at the bottom of any email.
© 2020 Univair Aircraft Corporation. Prices and availablility are subject to change without notice.
All product and company names are trademarks or registered trademarks of their respective owners. Univar's descriptive use does not imply any affiliation with or endorsement by the respective owners.
All prices are in USD.
Close
Close
Selected For Comparision
Compare Now
